Hello.
こんにちは
It's cute.
可愛いね
What is your name?
お名前何て言うんですか?
I'm Noah.
ノアです
Noah-chan.
ノアちゃん
Isn't this popular?
これモテるでしょ?
I'm not popular.
モテないです
Really?
本当に?
If you were in school, you'd be a real Madonna.
学校にいたらマジマドンナじゃん
Noah-chan, are you nervous?
ノアちゃん緊張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
It's exciting.
ドキドキするね
How old is Noah now?
今ノアちゃん何歳?
I'm 18 years old.
18歳です
18?
It's the most fun time.
一番楽しい時だね
What makes you happy?
何してる時の幸せ?
It's when I'm eating rice.
ご飯食べてる時です
What do you like?
何が好きだ?
Sushi.
お寿司
What kind of material do you like?
何のネタがいいの?
Salmon.
サーモン
You're young, I guess.
若いな、なんか
That's delicious, salmon.
美味しいよね、サーモン
How many centimeters are you tall?
身長は何センチある?
It is 158 cm.
158センチです
Where is this?
ここは?
This is a C cup.
ここはCカップです
C cup.
Cカップ
It looks very clean.
すごい清楚な見た目だね
Looks like an idol.
アイドルみたいじゃん
Do you like that?
そういうの好きなの?
I really like idols.
アイドル結構好きです
I like it.
好きなんだ
Which group do you like?
どのグループが好き?
Like Nogizaka.
野木坂とか
Because it's true.
だっていそうだもんな
You'll be told.
言われるでしょ
sometimes.
たまに
hey.
ね
What do you usually do on your days off?
いつも休みの日はさ、 何してるの?
I mostly watch anime.
大体アニメ見てます
anime?
アニメ?
What do you like?
何が好きなの?
I recently watched Summertime Render.
最近見たのは、 サマータイムレンダー
What is that?
何ですかそれは?
Time loop type?
タイムループ系?
Is it more interesting than One Piece?
ワンピースより面白いの?
It was quite interesting.
結構面白かったです
That's right.
そうなんだ
Yeah.
うん
So I always watch anime.
じゃあいつもアニメ見てるんだ
I always watch it.
いつも見てます
Haven't you gone out?
お出かけしてないの?
What do you do when you can't go out?
お出かけ止まれた時、 そん時は何して遊ぶの?
Eating and shopping.
ご飯食べたり、 買い物したり
Do you buy clothes?
お洋服買ったり?
Buying clothes.
お洋服買ったり
It's fun.
楽しいんだ
Now Non-chan is here, Noba-chan is now,
今のんちゃんはさ、 のばちゃんはさ、
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏いるの?
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏いないです
not present?
いない?
Why don't you make it?
なんで作んないの?
I can't have a boyfriend.
彼氏できない
Lie.
嘘つけ
You'll be popular if you have such a cute face.
モテるだろ、こんな可愛い顔したら
I can't have a boyfriend.
彼氏できないです
Do you have high ideals?
理想が高いのかな?
Maybe.
もしかして
What kind of man do you like?
どういう男の人が好きなの?
I like mature people.
大人っぽい人が好きです
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
I'm old enough.
歳いいんだ
I like being older.
年上がいいんです
How old can you go?
何歳くらいまでいけるの?
Can I get more than 10?
10個上とかもいける?
I can probably get 10 or more.
10個上とかも 多分いけます
Is it safe until the age of 28?
28歳までセーフか
I'm bored.
俺、ハセレてるね
I'm getting nervous.
緊張しちゃうね
Well then, please stand up for once.
じゃあ、一回立ってごらん
I like your great style.
すごいスタイルいいね
Are you doing any exercise or dieting?
何か運動とかダイエットしてるの?
I don't exercise.
運動はしてないね
I haven't.
してないんだ
Just food?
食事だけ?
I was careful.
気 をつけてんだ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Why is your skin so smooth?
なんでこんなお肌ツルツルなの?
That's amazing.
すごいね
Looks like an egg.
卵みたい
Genetic?
遺伝?
It's genetic.
遺伝ですね
遺伝なんだ
Hanging out, that.
つるみな、それ
Can you turn around?
後ろ向いてごらん?
Roma-chan, your legs are long.
ロマちゃん、足長いね
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Kuro-chan, turn this way.
ク ロちゃん、こっち向いて
nice to meet you.
初めまして
Hello, I'm Kuro-chan, a pervert.
どうも、変態のクロちゃんです
thank you.
よろしくお願いします
Please.
お願いしまーす
Are you excited?
ドキドキする?
How many men have you experienced?
男の人経験何人くらい?
There are 3 people.
3人です
Three people?
3人か
It's the fourth person.
4人目だね
Let me take it off the ribbon.
リボンから外してあげて
You have beautiful skin.
綺麗な肌やなー
It's really white.
本当に真っ白だね
Plus, it's wearing a really cute bottom.
しかも、めっちゃ可愛い下につけてるし
That glue looks good on you.
似合うな、そのグルー
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
No, I can't show it.
ダメだよ、見せない
Let me show you.
見せてごらん
My skin is really beautiful.
本当に肌きれいだわ
amazing.
すごい
Kuro-chan, this is exciting.
ク ロちゃん、これ興奮したね
Let the skirt flow.
スカート流してごらん
You have really beautiful skin.
すんごい綺麗な肌したぞ
It's below.
下になっちゃったね
How do you feel now?
今どんな気分?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Turn around.
後ろ向いて
Your butt is really big.
ちゃんとお尻おっきいね
Get your hands on that side.
そこの側に手ついてごらん
Stick out your ass.
お尻プリッとつき出して
Just turn your face towards me.
顔だけこっち向いて
Open your legs a little.
ちょっと足開いてごら
yeah.
ん
Kuro-chan, would you like to touch this butt?
ク ロ ちゃん、このお尻触ってみ?
It was really chewy there.
すんげーもちもちしたそこだね
Happy Kuro-chan, this is it.
幸せなクロちゃん、これ
You can stuff your face with that.
それ顔詰めていいよ
18 year old ass at the same time.
同時18歳のお尻
Highest.
最高
You really are a pervert, Kuro-chan.
本当変態なー、クロちゃん
Kuro-chan, how do you feel?
クロちゃん、どんな感じ?
Do you know what's happening?
何されてるか分かる?
My butt doesn't smell.
お尻くんくん匂いがない
He's the strongest pervert in history.
史上最強の変態でしょ
Keep an eye on me, Kuro-chan.
注視してごらん、クロちゃん
Kuro-chan, let's take a look at your boobs.
クロちゃん、 おっぱい見ちゃおうか
Please remove it slowly.
ゆっくりはずしてごらん
Are you so embarrassed that you hide it?
恥ずかしくて隠しちゃうの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
They really do feel like the boobs of an 18 year old.
ほんと18歳のおっぱいって感じしてるね
I've never been taken like this before.
こうやって取られたことなんてないでしょ
Will it become chewy?
もちもちしちゃう?
Kuro-chan, try touching your breasts.
クロちゃん、おっぱい触ってみて
Kubitsuman.
しくびつまん
What are you so nervous about?
何ビキビキしてるの?
Noga-chan is getting tired.
のがちゃん、しくび立ってきてる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
How does it feel to have your breasts touched?
おっぱい触られるとどういう気分になる?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Kuro-chan, you can suck on that for a second.
クロちゃん、ちょっとそれしゃぶっていいよ
You got your boobs sucked.
しゃぶられちゃったね、おっぱい
Look here.
こっち見て
I'm going to take a picture of my face with my breasts being thrown.
おっぱい投げられてる顔を写してく
Re.
れ
Kuro-chan, what does it taste like?
ク ロちゃん、どんな味する?
delicious?
おいしい?
Berdyef in the mouth.
口のベルディーフ
Does it make you feel stiff?
コリコリしちゃうの?
Kuro-chan, you're the best.
クロちゃん、最高だな
Kuro-chan, let's lick the embarrassing part.
クロちゃん、恥ずかしいとこ舐めてみようか
Let's open our arms like this.
腕をこうやって開いていこう
Armpits up.
脇上げ
Hold your elbows.
両肘抱えて
Hold your elbows and elbows.
自分の肘と肘を持って
Hold your elbows more.
もっと肘を持って
Do you want to crush it?
つぶったいの?
Try again.
もう一回やってみて
Her legs are cute.
足がかわいい
it hurts.
痛い
copper?
どう?
Kuro-chan, the taste of sweat.
クロちゃん、汗の味
delicious.
おいしい
Did it taste delicious?
おいしい味した?
Is there a place where you can be licked?
ここ舐められるとこある?
do not have.
ない
It's twisting and turning.
くねくねしてるもんだよ
Did it taste like 18 years old?
18歳の味した?
You have an erotic body.
エロい体してるな
Actually, don't you have a lot of boyfriends?
実は彼氏いっぱいいるんじゃないの?
On a night like this.
こんな夜は
You can definitely have it.
絶対持てるでしょ
Add boredom to that.
そこに退屈割りして
Do you go to the pants yourself?
自分でパンツに行くの?
My hair is growing properly.
ちゃんとお毛毛生えてるんだ
You have a really naughty body.
本当エッチな体してるね
I'm bored.
退屈割りしてる
I went further to the butt.
もっとお尻までいってきました
Until the last minute.
ギリギリまで
Now it opens slowly.
これでゆっくり開いたから
Your pussy was taken.
おまんこ取られちゃったね
I'm stepping here.
ここに足かけてる
both.
両 方
And my butt is even more tight.
で、お尻もっとギリギリまで
Have you ever done a pose like this?
こんなポーズしたことある?
It was my first time.
初めてした
Is this your first time?
初めてしちゃった?
Open it yourself.
自分で開いてごらん
My pussy is a little wet.
ちょっとおまんこ濡れてるよ
Please open it more.
もっと開いてごらん
Take a closer look at Flo-chan.
フロちゃん近くで見てごらん
This cute pussy is the best.
こんな可愛いこのまんこ最高じゃん
How do you feel now?
今どんな気分?
I can see deep inside.
奥の奥まで見えてるよ
What do you like about pussy?
おまんこはどこが好きなの?
I don't really understand?
あんまわかんない?
Don't you know?
わか んない?
Let's let it cool then.
じゃあ冷ましてみよっか
Flo-chan, keep an eye on her chest.
フロちゃん、くりに注視して
What does it taste like?
どんな味するの?
Lick it all from the bottom before it gets wet.
濡れてる前に下から全部舐めて
Belovero.
ベロベロって
Open your pussy.
おまんこ開けな
Tell me what's going on.
何されてるか言って
Stick your nose in everything below.
下で全部鼻突っ込んで
Lick it all inside.
中全部舐めてあげて
Nulston before licking.
舐める前からヌルストン
It's so nice.
こんなにようつんばいな
Stick out your butt.
お尻プリって突き出して
What's the shape of this butt, Flo-chan?
このお尻の形どうよ、フロちゃん
Do you know where it's taken now?
今どこ取られてるかわかる?
It's your butthole.
お尻の穴だよ
difficult?
難しい?
Show me more properly.
もっとちゃんと見せて
No, Flo-chan.
ダメだよ、フロちゃん
Open your legs.
足開いて
Stick your butt out more, Pri.
お尻もっと突き出して、プリ
Lick it all.
全部舐めて
Where did you get licked now?
今どこ舐められた?
I've never had my butt licked.
お尻舐められたことないし
Just give it a taste.
ちょっと味わってみなよ
You're stealing a lot for the first time.
いっぱい初めて奪っちゃってるね
The shape of your butt is beautiful.
お尻の形きれいだわ
I can't wait to include it, Gro-chan.
入れたくてたまんないね、グロちゃん
Did you get your ass licked again?
またお尻舐められたの?
Should I put my feet on my shoulders and get on the sofa over there?
肩が足、そこのソファーのところに乗っけちゃおうか
It's on the side.
横のところにね
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It doesn't stick out.
プリって突き出しておらん
Look at it all, look.
全部見なよ、ほら
Is it sticky?
くすぬったい?
Try to be patient with that.
我慢してみてよ、それ
Don't forget your pussy, Gro-chan.
おまんご忘れないでね、グロちゃん
I'll put all the flyers in my mouth.
ビラ全部口ん中入れちゃう
It's a manjiru zombie.
まんじるゾンビなんで
Are you licking my ass again?
またお尻舐めてんの?
Gro-chan,
グロちゃん、
It's about time I asked you to do something on this side.
そ ろそろこっち側もしてもらおうか
So
そ
Why don't you sit down?
こ 座ってごらん?
Can you sit on the floor?
床座ってもらえる?
Do you know what that thing in front of you is?
目の前にあるやつ何だか分かる?
Penis.
おちんち
Try squeezing tight.
ぎゅっといってごらん?
Is it warm?
あったかい?
there were
あった
shellfish.
か い
Well, let me show you that slowly.
じゃあ それ、ゆっくり見せてもらう
What's your penis?
どうおちんち?
It's moving.
動いてる
Is it moving?
動いてる?
Have you seen it for the first time in a while?
久しぶりに見た?
Try moving your face closer.
もっと顔近づけてみてごらん
Try smelling it.
おにおい嗅いでみて
Do you smell something?
何か匂いする?
Softener.
柔軟剤
Have a clean penis.
清潔なちんちになる
Are you touching it a lot?
いっぱい触っておいてる?
What happened to your penis?
おちんちどうなってきた?
It's getting bigger.
大きくなってきた
Has it gotten bigger?
大きくなってきたか?
Did you happen to touch it?
たまたま触っておいて?
Use both hands.
両手使って
It's getting big.
でっかくなってきたね
Do you like big dicks?
おっきいちんちに好き?
Try applying it to this cute face.
このかわいい顔に当ててごらん
Have you ever been hit like this?
こんなにやられたことある?
Is it as big as your face?
顔と同じくらいでっかい?
Please take a minute earlier.
さっき分中してごらん
Stretch it out here.
こっちに伸ばして
Try and hang out as hard as you can.
もっと思いっきりペーってぶら出して
Just suck it.
しゃぶってごらん
I don't know.
どうかもしれない
Stretch it into Noba-chan's mouth.
のばちゃんの口に伸ばして
Highest?
最高?
Please suck me more.
もっとしゃぶってもらえ
It's a huge mess.
すっごいごだれだね
various.
い ろ いろ
I'm getting wet all over my dick.
ちんちにびしょびしょになっちゃう
Suck it even more.
もっと多くまでしゃぶって
Is it too big to fit in?
おっきくて入んない?
It felt so good.
いっぱい気持ちよくしたね
You look cute when you're sucking.
しゃぶってる顔かわいいね
Pelopon from the root.
根元からぺろぽんって
The part where you take a decent crack and throw it in your mouth.
まともパクって口に投げるところ
Erotic face.
エロい顔
I also happen to throw the opposite.
反対もたまたま投げて
I'm about to throw it all into my mouth.
全部口に投げるところ
My penis is soaked.
ちんちにびしょって
Let's get a lot of spit out.
も っとツバいっぱい出して
Just look at me.
ちぼうちぼうしてごらん
Sutto, Chin-chi.
すって、ちんち
painful?
苦しい?
Your mouth is full of dick.
口に中、ちんちいっぱいだね
Please spit more on me.
もっといっぱいつばたらしてごらん
It's all in my mouth.
すごくまで入ってんね、口に
This guy makes me feel good.
気持ちよくなっちゃう、こいつ
Suck such a cute face.
こんなにかわいい顔しゃぶる
Sucks a lot.
いっぱいしゃぶる
Noga-chan's face is so cute when she's sucking it.
のがちゃんしゃぶってる顔かわいいよ
A lot of everything.
いっぱい全部だね
It's delicious.
おいしいね
Chinchipanpanjan, this guy.
ちんちぱんぱんじゃん、こいつ
Isn't your dick delicious?
ちんちおいしいでしょ?
Try saying it.
言ってみて
Chinchi is delicious.
ちんちおいしい
cute.
かわいい
Take a look at Kitopanpan.
きとうぱんぱんでごらん
Take it back to your hands.
手へどいてごらん
Just my mouth.
口だけ
Let's hang out more.
もっとちぼうちぼうして
You can use your hands too.
手も使っていいよ
Make yourself feel good.
いっぱい気持ちよくして
Spit on it and dribble on it.
つばたらして、ちぼうちぼうして
Chinbou.
ちんぼう
It's all over the place, all around you.
べろだして、きとうのまわり全部だね
Finally have the skin
最後に肌を持って
Go.
行 って
It has been destroyed.
したばれてきた
Kura-chan moves a lot.
いっぱい動かす、くらちゃん
Chibo is included to the end.
ちぼうあくまで入ってるね
I burst into tears.
涙になりちゃった
Face and dazzle.
顔とくらみて
Kura-chan, what should we do?
くらちゃん、どうする?
Will you bully me?
いじめるか?
Shall we tease you?
いじめようか
Noga-chan, let's go to bed.
のがちゃん、ベッド行こう
Just lie there.
そこ横になってごらん
Kura-chan, can I do whatever I want?
くらちゃん、好きなのしていい?
I tried opening my legs more last time.
もっと前回、足開いてみる
Kura-chan, put your finger in there too.
くらちゃん、指も入れて
What's going on inside?
中どうなってる?
Pichopicho.
ぴちょぴちょ
Is it wet?
ぬれてる?
You look cute.
かわいい顔してる
You're wet, Kura-chan.
ぬれぬれたね、くらちゃん
It's a chestnut.
くりしゃぶりのね
Homanko, does it feel good?
ほまんこ、気持ちいいの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Kura-chan, do you want to use that?
くらちゃん、あれ使うか?
Shall we do that?
そうしようか
Have you ever used this?
これ使ったことある?
Shall we discipline you?
い じ め よう か
Right.
じゃん
Not really.
ないね
Up to this point?
これ点まで?
Can I show my pussy?
ほまんこ出ていいかな?
Awesome.
すんごい
It's getting better.
くり立ってきたね
The bottle was open.
びんびんのくりがあってたね
My face is starting to feel good.
気持ちいい顔になってきてる
Chestnut, it's getting bigger.
くり、大きくなってきたよ
I'm pouring it into it.
ぶち込んでます
It's small, so go.
ちっちゃいから、いって
It's tough.
きついよ
It's too tight and stops.
きつすぎて止まっちゃう
Is this inside your pussy?
ほまんこの中入ってるの?
It's tough, isn't it?
きついでしょ
He said he swallowed it.
飲み込んだって
It's too tight and it comes out.
きつすぎて出てきちゃう
It'll stop.
止まっちゃう
Shall I put that in?
あれ入れるか?
Have you ever put this in?
これ入れたことある?
Isn't there?
ないの?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
Does it feel weird?
変な感じ?
I'm falling right in here.
ほまんこの中落ちてられてる
It feels good.
気持ちいいな
I swallowed it.
飲み込んじゃったよ
Erotic juice is coming out.
エロい汁出てきてる
Look down.
下見て
yes.
はい
Do you understand?
わかる?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ
You look amazing.
すんげー気持ちいい顔してる
Please give me a little pisson.
ちょっとピッソンしてあげてください
Feels good.
気持ちいい
She has a very sexy face.
すんごいエロい顔してる
Is it possible?
できそう?
Okay, try it.
よし、してごらん
Oh, amazing.
あ、すっごい
I was talking about the first time.
初めての場合を言っちゃったよ
Hello, look at me.
どうも、ほまんこ見て
Try opening it.
開いてみて
Your pussy is soaking wet.
びっしょぬれじゃん、ほまんこ
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
I couldn't resist.
我慢できなかった
I'm determined to put on a nice face.
気持ちいい顔する覚悟じゃん
Become more intense.
もっと激しくなって
Inhale properly deep inside.
奥までちゃんと吸い込んで
It's delicious, big dick.
おいしいでしょ、おっきいちんちゃん
Please suck more.
もっといっぱいしゃぶってください
Don't stop.
やめちゃダメだよ
While licking.
舐めつつ
Please move your hand away.
手をどかしてごらん
Let me spit on you.
ツバ垂らしてもらって
Have a good chat.
いいしゃべりして
You're huge, Kuro-chan.
でっかいね、黒ちゃん
It's hard, isn't it?
固いでしょ
I happened to give it to you.
たまたまもんであげた
Are you doing your best to suck it?
頑張ってしゃぶってんの
Big dick.
おっきいちんちゃん
Really suck just the tip.
先っぽだけほんとしゃぶって
The tip is jiggly.
先っぽじぼじぼして
Stroke a lot of people.
人をいっぱい撫であげて
Hold my legs and suck them.
足抱えてしゃぶってあげて
Don't let go.
離しちゃダメだよ
Hold me tight.
ぎゅーって抱えて
Kuro-chan, have me push up from below.
黒ちゃん、下から突き上げてもらう
It's big and painful, isn't it?
大きくて苦しいでしょ
Kuro-chan, shall we come in soon?
黒ちゃん、そろそろ入れるか
Let's do that
そうしよう
mosquito.
か
Well then, let's face this way.
じゃあ こっち向いておこう
Just sit on top of this dick.
このちんこの上またまってごらん
She's a child who carries her own penis.
自分でちんちん持って入れる子なの
Big penis.
おっきいちんちん
I hope you feel a lot better.
いっぱい気持ちよくなってごらん
Rub it all over your pussy.
おまんこいっぱいこすりつけて
Don't stop.
やめちゃダメだよ
It's all in there until bedtime.
寝元まで全部入ってるよ
That's hard, dick.
固いね、ちんちん
Beautiful butt shape.
お尻の形きれい
Try to fall forward.
体前に倒れてみ
Kuro-chan, push up from below.
黒ちゃん、下から突き上げて
Rub it hard.
激しくこすりつけて
Even if two people face each other.
2人向き合っても
Does your dick feel good?
ちんちん気持ちよいですか?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
There's a lot in it.
すごすご入ってるよ
There's a penis in it.
ちんちん入ってるよ
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Shall we do the one facing backwards?
後ろ向きのやつやるか
Stay on top of this.
この上またまってね
The one with a dick in it again.
またちんちん入ってるやつ
Even if you stab it deep inside.
奥までブサッと刺しても
It's better to spread your legs wider.
もっと足広げたほうがいっきり
You're amazing.
お前すごいよ
Move your hips and look up.
腰を動かしてごらん上に
Kuro-chan, follow me from below.
黒ちゃん、ついても下から
More legs.
もっと足にして
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
I'm still going.
まだいっちゃうんだよ
Are you going?
いっちゃうの?
Kuro-chan, hurry up.
黒ちゃんもっと早く
Move your hips more.
も っと腰を動かしてね
A big penis feels good, right?
大きいちんちん気持ちいいでしょ?
Do you like this?
これ好きなの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
If I can take your dick, I will do it over and over again.
ちんちんいられると何回もいっちゃうんだよ
That's tough, Kuro-chan.
きついでしょ、黒ちゃん
Kuro-chan, I'm going to stab you with a sense of humor.
黒ちゃん、文気してブッ刺してやる
Black-chan stabbed all the way to the root.
根元までブッ刺して黒ちゃん
Hold your arm and don't bite.
腕をもって、かんづきしないで
Did you go again?
またいっちゃったの?
With a dick.
ちんちんで
Look what's inside.
入ってるとこ見てごらん
appear?
見える?
It's huge.
でっかい入ってるよ
I'll do it normally.
正常やっちゃう
You're using your legs as hard as you can.
足思いっきりだね
I'll stab you all the way to the root.
根元までブッ刺してやる
Open your legs as wide as you can.
思いっきり足開いて
amazing.
すごい
Does it feel good there?
そこ気持ちいいの?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I want you to stab me more and more.
もっといっぱいちんこ刺してもらう
Kuro-chan, open your legs.
黒ちゃん、足開いて
more
もっと
I'll stab you as hard as I can.
い っぱい刺してあげる
Kuro-chan, hold on to your limits.
黒ちゃん、限界まで我慢して
I'll give it all, Kuro-chan.
全部出すよ、黒ちゃん
I will cum inside you.
中出していく
I'll save up a lot and then take it out.
いっぱい溜めてから出すね
Not yet.
まだだめ
Did you take it all out?
全部出した?
It came out.
出てきた
That's a lot, Kuro-chan.
いっぱいだね、黒ちゃん
Wake up!
起きてごらん
Chin chin.
ちんちん
Finally, can you put it away neatly?
最後、きれいにしまえる?
Go deep and clean it.
奥までくらえてきれいにして
Was it clean?
きれいにできた?
Kuro-chan, how about the end?
黒ちゃん、最後はどう?
Moa-chan, how was your day?
モアちゃん、どうだった、今日は?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It was so cute today.
すごい可愛かったよ、今日
Let's hide and invite you to our house again.
また隠れてお家さんさんと誘おうね
In secret.
内 緒で
bye bye.
バイバイ